shophunk.com 2014-05-31

# Shophunk | The Best Online shopping portal In India for Branded Electronics, Mobiles,Accessories, Apparels, Footwear ,Books

  * Protecting your privacy is very important to us. We have accordingly developed this Privacy Policy to protect your personal information and keep it confidential. We endeavour to comply with laws of other countries but cannot and do not warrant that we do. We do everything we reasonably can to protect your rights of privacy on systems and the Website controlled by us, but we are not liable for any unauthorised or unlawful disclosures of your personal and confidential information made by third parties who are not subject to our control, for example advertisers and websites that have links to our Website. You should take note that the information and privacy practices of our business partners, advertisers, sponsors or other sites to which we provide hyperlinks, may be different from ours. Our privacy policy is subject to change at any time without notice. To make sure you are aware of any changes, please review this policy periodically. 
  *  
  * We categorize information about you (collectively referred to as "Personal Information") as follows:
  *  
  * **Personal Information**
  *   * Seajin Technology is the sole owner of the website Shophunk.com. Seajin Technology respects your privacy. This Privacy Policy provides the manner your data is collected and used by shophunk.com. You are advised to please read the Privacy Policy carefully. By accessing the services provided by shophunk.com you agree to the collection and use of your data by shophunk.com in the manner provided in this Privacy Policy.
  *  
  * **Log information:**
  *   * Information such as your web request, IP address, browser type, browser language, date and time of request.
  *  
  * **Service Usage**
  *   * Information about your navigation using our Services, for example the URLs of websites, which you visit and from which you request downloads.
  *  
  * **Transactional Information:**
  *   * Transactional history (other than banking details) about your e-commerce activities.
  *  
  * **User IDs :**
  *   * Your usernames, passwords, email addresses and other security-related information used by you in relation to our Services.
  *  
  * **Cookies**
  *   * A "cookie" is a small piece of information stored by a Web server on a Web browser so it can be later read back from that browser. Cookies are useful for enabling the browser to remember information specific to a given user. shophunk.com places both permanent and temporary cookies in your computer. shophunk.com cookies do not contain any of your personally identifiable information.
  *  
  * **How is the information used...?**
  *   * We use your personal information to help us provide personalized features tailor our sites to your interest for promotional offers through our business associates and partners to get in touch with you when necessary to provide the services requested by you to preserve social history as governed by existing law or policy We use contact information internally to direct our efforts for product improvement contact you as a survey respondent notify you if you win any contest and send you promotional materials from our contest sponsors or advertisers
  *  
  * **With whom will your information be shared**
  *   * We will not use your financial information for any purpose other than to complete a transaction with you. We do not rent, sell or share your personal information and we will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information to third parties unless: we have your permission to provide products or services you've requested it is shared with our business associates and partners for promotional offers. to help investigate, prevent or take action regarding unlawful and illegal activities, suspected fraud, potential threat to the safety or security of any person, violations of ShopasUlike.com?s terms of use or to defend against legal claims; special circumstances such as compliance with subpoenas, court orders, requests/order from legal authorities or law enforcement agencies requiring such disclosure.
  *  
  * **Security Precautions**
  *   * Our site has stringent security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Whenever you change or access your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. Once your information is in our possession we adhere to strict security guidelines, protecting it against unauthorized access.
  *  
  * **Links to Other Sites**
  *   * Our site links to other websites that may collect personally identifiable information about you. getZinga.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those linked websites.
  *
